playtexfits.com 2014-06-25

# Playtex | Privacy Policy

LAST UPDATED: OCTOBER 21, 2013

At **Hanesbrands Inc.** ("Hanesbrands"), we respect our customers and understand that you may have concerns about privacy, so we have instituted privacy policies intended to ensure that your personal information is handled safely and responsibly.

This Privacy Policy Statement sets forth the privacy policy pertaining to this website, [www.Playtexfits.com](http://www.playtexfits.com/) (the "Site"), which is owned by Hanesbrands and to other Internet sites on which this Privacy Policy Statement is posted. By using this Site, you expressly accept and agree to be bound by and abide by the terms set forth in this Privacy Policy Statement. For other terms and conditions that apply to your use of the Site, please review our Terms of Use. Any terms that are not defined in this Privacy Policy Statement shall have the meaning given in the Terms of Use. This Privacy Policy Statement applies only to "Personal Information" that we collect on-line. For purposes of this Privacy Policy Statement, "Personal Information" means any information you provide to us on the Site which can personally identify you and may include your first/middle initial or name and last name, street address, town or city, state, zip code, telephone number, fax number, instant-messenger nickname, blog or other personal website URL, age, date of birth, e-mail address, credit card or debit card information, demographics, size, brand preferences and purchase information that is linked to your personally identifiable information, and any other information which can personally identify you.

Unless otherwise provided herein, any reference to "Hanesbrands," "we," "us" and "our" shall mean and include Hanesbrands, it subsidiaries, affiliates, operating divisions and brands (collectively, "affiliates").

**YOUR CALIFORNIA PRIVACY RIGHTS:** Residents of the State of California have the right to request a list of all third parties to which we have disclosed their personal information during the preceding year for direct marketing purposes. If you are a California resident and request information about the disclosure of your Personal Information, you must send a request to the following address with a preference on how our response to your request should be sent (email or postal mail). Send an email to the Privacy Administrator at [webmaster@Playtexfits.com](mailto:webmaster@Playtexfits.com) or you may contact us via postal mail at: Playtex Consumer Services, Hanesbrands Inc., P.O. Box 3013, Winston-Salem, NC 27102.

**Overview: This Privacy Policy Statement is intended to explain our privacy practices and inform you as to:**

  * **The kinds of Personal Information we collect from users of the Site and how that information is collected;**
  * **How we use your Personal Information;**
  * **The circumstances under which we disclose Personal Information to third parties;**
  * **How you can access, update or delete Personal Information collected about you by us on the Site;**
  * **The mechanisms we have implemented to protect your Personal Information; and**
  * **That we may choose to disclose nonpublic personal information about you to a third party for compensation.**

**Behavioral Advertising: Advertisements displayed to you on this Web Site and elsewhere may be customized to your interests and preferences, based on your Personal Information and Site usage information, including (but not limited to) non-personally identifying information, which may be obtained from you or from other sources. Our Site does not honor "do-not-track" settings in your web browser. Instead, to opt out of behavioral advertising, visit<http://www.aboutads.info/choices>. However, if you opt out we may still suggest products to you based on other products you have viewed on our sites.**

**Information Hanesbrands Collects**

Hanesbrands collects Personal Information about you on the Site only when you submit it to us, such as when registering on our site, subscribing to our e-mail program, submitting a review or question, participating in special functions of the Site, such as e-cards, public forums, shopping lists, wish lists or games, responding to a survey, submitting applications, entering a sweepstakes or contest, or making testimonials, suggestions or comments.

You may be able to send information about our products and services to your friends and family members through our site by clicking on an "E-mail to Friend" or similar "share" button on our site or in an e-mail that we have sent you. In some of these cases (unless you simply forward our e-mail on your own), you may provide the name and e-mail address of your friend or family member to us. Such information will be treated in accordance with this Privacy Policy and applicable law.

In addition, when you access the Site our web servers may automatically recognize and collect information regarding your IP address, referring domain, your type of internet browser, operating system software, screen resolution, cookie preferences and similar technical data. None of this information is personally identifiable.

Technology: When you access the Site, our web servers may automatically recognize and collect non-personally identifiable information. We use technology (e.g., small data files that may be stored on your computer that are referred to as 'cookies,' electronic image requests known as "web beacons" or "single-pixel gifs", and files stored on your computer called "local shared objects"). Some of this technology can recognize you as you browse or when you return to our Site. Technology may also collect the type of operating system and browser you are using and accumulate and report anonymous, statistical information on Site usage. Technology shows us how our customers use our Site and allow us to give you a more personalized experience when you use our Site. These types of technology generally do not collect, gather, monitor or share any Personal Information; they are used to compile anonymous information about Site usage. We do not use technology to detect or collect Personal Information, but we may combine the data collected by this technology with Personal Information you do give us in order to send you information that may be of interest. Some Internet browsers allow you to change the settings and stop it from automatically accepting certain technology such as cookies. Some media players, such as Flash, allow you to manage local shared objects. If you do change these settings, it may affect your ability to use certain features and functions on our Site and you may need to re-enter information when you browse or when you return to our Site. You should consult with the publisher or licensor of your browser and media players if you want to change the settings or are experiencing trouble browsing our Site.

**By using our Site, you consent to our use of tracking technologies as described above.**

Minors: We recognize the particular importance of protecting the privacy of Personal Information where children are involved. We do not knowingly collect Personal Information from children under the age of 13. If a child under the age of 13 has provided our website with personally identifiable information, we ask that such child's parent or guardian call 800-225-4872 or contact us at [webmaster@Playtexfits.com](mailto:webmaster@Playtexfits.com) and we will delete the information about the child from our files.

**How Hanesbrands Uses the Information**

We may use your Personal Information for the following purposes:

  * to respond to your requests (including, for example, to enter a sweepstakes; post a testimonial, photograph, comment or question, or to receive product information, or catalogs or to enroll in our email program)
  * to improve the content, appearance and utility of the Site
  * to trace our visitors' use of the Site for internal research purposes
  * to invite you to participate in market research
  * to provide any necessary notices to our visitors and to notify our visitors of updates to the Site
  * to send catalogs, printed materials, offers and other announcements to postal addresses and to allow our affiliates and other reputable third party marketers to do the same
  * to send e-mail offers, announcements, or newsletters to your e-mail address (these emails may come from any of us at Hanesbrands, including any Hanesbrands affiliate)

If we publish Postings that you submit to us or our social media pages for potential publication, we may identify you as the source of such information by first name, last initial and city of residence or as otherwise indicated on the applicable submission pages. Any information about yourself submitted in a "public" area or feature of our Site or our social media pages, may allow members of the general public to view such submitted information and content on the Internet, may be routed through our servers, the servers of one or more third parties on our behalf, and the Internet, **and you have no expectation of or right to privacy with regard to any such Posting**. The security of any information you disclose in public areas or features of the Site is not guaranteed; you make such Postings and disclosures at your own risk.

**Disclosure to Third Parties**

We will not rent your email address. In addition, we do not sell your Personal Information to unaffiliated entities, except in the limited circumstances described below. **Remember, we are referring to information obtained online through our Site and the use of it for email or other online purposes.** We may disclose Personal Information to affiliates for marketing and/or administrative purposes, and you may opt-out of such disclosure for marketing purposes. With your consent, or if you provide your contact information to one of our e-commerce web sites, we may rent lists of our customers' postal mailing addresses to third parties. You can elect for us not to rent these lists to unaffiliated third parties by emailing us at [webmaster@Playtexfits.com](mailto:webmaster@Playtexfits.com). Some of our contests, sweepstakes and other offerings may be co-sponsored by another company. In those situations, the information we obtain from you in connection with them may be shared with our co-sponsor. In those situations, our co-sponsors will have the right to use your information for their own purposes, in accordance with their own policies. We are not responsible for how our co-sponsors may use your information.

Third parties, such as ad networks, web analytics companies and social networking platforms, collect personally identifiable information about your online activities over time and across our Site and other third-party online properties or online services.

Additionally, we may disclose your Personal Information if required to do so by law or to comply with our legal and regulatory obligations or to protect our Site, our business and assets, or other users of our Site or the public, in general. On occasion, we contract with other companies to provide certain services to us, including credit card processing, shipping, e-mail distribution, changing mailing addresses, market research and promotions management. We provide these companies only with the information (which may include Personal Information) needed to perform their services and try to ensure your Personal Information is maintained and used as set forth in this Privacy Policy Statement. These companies are prohibited from using your Personal Information for their own marketing purposes or from sharing this information with others, but we cannot guarantee security of Personal Information and are not liable for misuse of it by others. Hanesbrands may (a) buy or sell assets, subsidiaries, or business units, or may be acquired by another company or (b) file for or be subject to an involuntary bankruptcy or restructuring. In such transactions, Personal Information is usually one of the transferred business assets, and we reserve the right to transfer all Personal Information in our possession as part of any such transaction. Such transferred Personal Information shall remain subject to the promises made in this Privacy Policy Statement.

**Updating Your Personal Information; E-mail Unsubscribe Options**

If you registered on our Site, and in the event the Site does not have a "My Account" link to pages containing the Personal Information you wish to access, you may request that: (i) we correct or update any such Personal Information; or (ii) such Personal Information be unsubscribed from the email marketing database for the Site. To make such a request, you may click here or write to Playtex Consumer Services, Hanesbrands Inc., P.O. Box 3013, Winston-Salem, NC 27102. When contacting us, please be sure to provide us with your exact e-mail address, name, postal address, and/or telephone number(s) in order to be sure we handle your request correctly.

In addition each time we send you an e-mail marketing message, we give you the option to unsubscribe from the applicable brand's promotional e-mail list by simply clicking the unsubscribe link. We may, however, continue to contact you via e-mail for administrative or informational purposes, including follow-up messages regarding the administration of your account, any services, features or functions you have enrolled in or registered to use, any promotions or contests you have participated in or have entered, goods and/or services you have ordered, or other transactions you have undertaken with the Site.

**Third-Party Sites**

The Site may contain advertisements, references and links to other websites and third parties. We may also use third parties (i) to host and display our branded social media fan pages (e.g., Facebook, Twitter and YouTube), or (ii) to display or serve advertising on the Site and our web-based newsletters or other communications which you may choose to receive. Even if we have a relationship with the third party, we do not control those third-party sites or their privacy practices. **This Privacy Policy Statement does not cover any use of Personal Information that a third party may collect from you or that you make available via one of our branded social media pages on a third-party platform, such as Facebook. When you participate in our user community platforms at third party sites such as Facebook, the information you submit will be received and used by such third party platforms, pursuant to their privacy policies, and may also be received by us for our use in accordance with this Privacy Policy.**

**Security**

We maintain reasonable standards of security and confidentiality. However, for most Internet sites, it is possible that third parties may unlawfully intercept or access transmissions or private communications over an unsecured transmission or stored on our systems. We conduct financial transactions via secured transmissions but may not always secure other parts of the Site. We also limit access to the Site by our own employees to those individuals who are authorized for the proper handling of such information and any employee found violating our standards of security and confidentiality will be subject to our disciplinary processes. We request that our operational service providers follow the same policy.

**Phishing**

Phishing attacks attempt to steal consumers' personal identity data and financial account credentials. "Phishers" use "spoofed" e-mails to lead consumers to counterfeit websites designed to trick recipients into divulging sensitive Personal Information such as credit card numbers, account usernames, passwords, and Social Security Numbers. **WE DO NOT SEND EMAILS ASKING YOU TO PROVIDE OR CONFIRM SENSITIVE PERSONAL INFORMATION OR YOUR USERNAME OR PASSWORD!** If you receive such e-mail communication, please forward it immediately to the Site's Privacy Administrator at [webmaster@Playtexfits.com](mailto:webmaster@Playtexfits.com) and then immediately delete the fraudulent e-mail from your computer.

**Updating the Privacy Policy Statement**

As we continue to develop our Site and take advantage of technologies to improve the services we provide, we may have a need to change our current privacy policies. We therefore reserve the right, at our discretion, to change, modify, add, or remove portions of this Privacy Policy Statement at any time. If elements of our Privacy Policy Statement change, we will revise this Privacy Policy Statement. You should check this page periodically for changes. Your continued use of this Site following the posting of changes to this Privacy Policy Statement will mean that you accept those changes. Under certain circumstances (for example, in connection with certain material changes), we may also elect to notify you of changes or updates to our Privacy Policy, or to request your consent for such changes, by additional means, such as posting a notice on the front page of our Web Site to sending you an e-mail.

**Questions Regarding This Privacy Policy Statement**

If you have questions about this Privacy Policy Statement, please contact our Privacy Administrator via e-mail at [webmaster@Playtexfits.com](mailto:webmaster@Playtexfits.com), call 800-225-4872 or mail your question or inquiry to Playtex Consumer Services, Hanesbrands Inc., P.O. Box 3013, Winston-Salem, NC 27102.
